他以前真的...
你在冒汗啊
You're sweating.
你为何如此紧张
Why are you nervous?
真主阿拉已经为你选好了道路
Allah himself has mapped out your path,
他不想让其追随者受到任何伤害
and he wouldn't want any harm to come to his believers,
对吧
would he?
朱海瑞有一个请求
Al-Zuhari has a request.
让他打个电话就行了
Make life a lot easier
何必这么麻烦
if he could pick up the phone, huh?
朱海瑞一定非常信任你
Al-Zuhari must trust you very much
才会让你来这送信
to have let you carry this message.
你会得到奖励的
You are to be rewarded.
在这等着
Wait here.
嘭
Kaboom.
吃午餐吗
Lunch?
黎巴嫩  贝鲁特
很高兴见到你  埃米尔
我听说那很快就要发生了
朱海瑞即将...
这种事不能明说
原谅我
我的激动无以言表
抱歉
有什么口信吗
必须把钱付给那苏格兰人
叛徒
你们暴露了
You've been made.
妈的
Fuck.
B组  埃米尔要抓活的
Bravo Team, I want Amir alive.
这里到处都是真主党党旗
There's a lot of Hezbollah yellow out here.
这城市归他们管  如果跟他们纠缠下去
They run the city. If we tangle with them--
把他抓回来  这是命令
You will bring him in. That's an order.
明白
Copy that.
-在后面  -谢了
- Out the back. - Thanks.
总部  我刚杀了个真主党警卫
Zero, one Hezbollah guard KIA.
没办法  不是他死就是我活
Sorry. It was him or me.
知道了
Roger.
B2  我已到达后院
Bravo Two, I'm out back.
B1  目标正在向你靠近
Bravo One, target coming to you.
收到
Yeah. Roger.
目标已擒
Target acquired.
把他带回来
Get the target back here.
明白
Roger.
咱们撤
Let's move.
怎么这么慢
What kept you?
下楼梯  快
Down those stairs. Move.
总部  我们遭到攻击  无法撤退
Zero, we're taking fire. Exit's no good.
B3  我们正在后退
Bravo three, we're falling back.
收到  我正在掉头
Copy that. I'm circling around.
-站起来  该死  斯科特  -妈的
- Stand up! Stand up! Shit. Scott. - Fuck.
目标中枪  撑不住了
Target's been gut-shot. He's never gonna make it.
你们准备在现场进行审讯
You're prepped for a field interrogation.
在车里可以  这里不行
In the fucking van, not here.
我们正遭到猛烈攻势
We're under heavy fire.
-你们必须进行审讯  -该死
- You will interrogate the prisoner. - Shit.
喂  看着我
Oi, look at me.
那个苏格兰人的名字叫莱瑟比  对吧
The Scotsman's name is Leatherby, right?
为什么要给他钱
What's he being paid for?
该死  武装敌军正在进入大楼
Shit. Armed x-rays entering the building.
好吧  看到这个账户了吗
OK. See this? See this account?
这是你们的交易记录
Those are your transactions,
都是中情局买的单
paid for by the CIA.
那不是我的
That is not mine.
-不是?  -是你伪造的
- Not? - You forged them.
看到这个了吗
You see this?
这是你的护照
See, this is your passport, proof of travel
是你在美国和以色列之间往返的凭据
between the United States of America and Israel.
我要死了
I'm dying.
总部  这家伙是不会开口的
Zero, this guy's not gonna talk.
把文件放到他口袋里
Put the papers in his pocket.
妈的
Fuck.
该死
Shit.
告诉他真主党会杀了他的家人
Tell him Hezbollah will take his family.
妈的
Fuck.
该死
Shit.
要是他们在你身上找到这些
They find these on you,
他们会杀了你的家人
they're gonna kill your family.
你看着办
Make a choice.
阿迈  楼下有动静
Mikey, we got some action downstairs.
迈克  我们得离开这
Mike, come on. We got to move.
喂  我们得赶快离开  迈克
Hey, come on. We got to move, Mike.
你把这些文件毁掉
You destroy the papers,
我就告诉你想知道的事
I tell you what you wish to know.
撤
Move!
快走
Come on.
我们现在真的需要接应
We're really ready to be picked up right now.
你们还没完成任务
You're not finished.
给我弄点有用的情报
Find me something concrete!
斯科特  打火机给我
Scott, your lighter.
她简直是疯了
She's fucking losing it.
把打火机扔给我
Throw me your lighter.
现在真是抽烟的好时候
Fucking fine time to start smoking.
没错  多谢关心
Yeah. Great. Nice of you to care.
看好了
Look.
B3  你在什么位置
Bravo Three, what's your position?
还有两分钟可以撤退
Exfil, two minutes.
你的家人安全了  说
Your family is safe. Talk.
真主原谅我  这是为他们好
Allah forgive me. This is for them.
他要来了
He's coming...
从叙利亚来
from Syria.
莱瑟比要带他来了
He's coming. Leatherby's bringing him.
谁  谁要从叙利亚过来
Who? Who's coming from Syria?
莱瑟比要从叙利亚带谁过来
Who's Leatherby bringing from Syria?
朱...
Al-Zu--
朱海瑞  朱海瑞
Al-Zuhari. Al-Zuhari.
总部  莱瑟比要带朱海瑞过来
Zero, Leatherby's bringing in Al-Zuhari.
朱海瑞要从叙利亚过来
Al-Zuhari's coming in from Syria.
听到了吗
Did you get that?
朱海瑞会从叙利亚过来
Al-Zuhari's coming in from Syria.
我就知道
I fucking knew it.
佩里德尔基诺  莫斯科西南部
请节哀
我的老友
维克多
是个好孩子
我的眼线说
他们是英国军方的人
做该做的事
Do what has to be done.
目的地: 贝鲁特
航班号:OA0547  日期:27日  起飞时间:上午10点
喂  喂
Oi, oi.
道尔顿他妈的哪去了
Oi, where the fuck is Dalton?
现在不是时候
Not now.
什么叫"现在不是时候"
What do you mean, not now?
发生了什么你都看到了
You saw what happened out there.
她差点害我们丧命
She nearly got us killed.
对  我站你们这边
No. I'm on your side.
没错  说得没错
It's true. Yeah. It's true, all right?
但她也挖出了朱海瑞的消息
But she also got us Al-Zuhari.
万一他在说谎怎么办  迈克尔
Yeah, and what happens if he's lying, Michael?
他没说谎
He wasn't lying.
你他妈最好没说错
You want to be fucking right.
听到了吗
You hear me?
我别无选择
I had no choice.
光天化日之下在大黑街头搞枪战
A street battle in Daheih in broad daylight?
白厅  伦敦
要是真主党盯着你们不放
How do you expect to operate effectively
你们还怎么开展行动
with Hezbollah breathing down your neck?
麻烦告诉我  你这烂摊子至少有些成果
Please tell me you got something to show for this mess.
埃米尔供出了朱海瑞
Amir gave us Al-Zuhari.
他会从叙利亚来这
He's coming into the city from Syria.
如果朱海瑞开始行动
Well, if Al-Zuhari's moving,
不管他在计划什么  很快就会付诸实施
then whatever he's planning must be happening soon.
詹姆士·莱瑟比会带他穿越边境
James Leatherby's bringing him across the border.
我们需要知道时间地点
We need to know time and location.
假设你的情报准确
Well, assuming your intel's good,
下一步准备怎么办
what's your next move?
卡马里本应付款给他
Kamali is supposed to pay him.
让他付
Let him.
你知道我不信任卡马里
You know that I don't trust Kamali.
瑞秋  卡马里是我们最好的突破口
Listen, Rachel, Kamali's the best thing we've got.
让他付款  看他能带什么情报给我们
You let him make the payment, see what he can get us,
上校  人员伤亡已经够惨重了
and, Major, we've lost enough men.
别逼我再回贝鲁特
Don't make me come back to Beirut.
我能向你保证
I can guarantee you...
万一他说谎怎么办  迈克尔
What happens if he's lying, Michael?
911事件前  基地组织也干过
...Al-Qaeda did before 9/11.
抓住卡马里就等于抓到了朱海瑞
We get Kamali, we get Al-Zuhari himself.
这是一次有条不紊的大清洗...
This is a systematic cleansing of the...
朱海瑞
Al-Zuhari.
今天发生的事简直...
What happened out there today
一团糟
was a mess.
我说过我能应付得了
I told you I could handle it.
你们的人根本不应该出现
Your people should never have been there.
埃米尔是我在行动方面的联络人
Amir was my contact on the operational side.
如果你不让我用自己的方法做事...
If you don't let me do things my way--
朱海瑞将会从叙利亚来这
Al-Zuhari is being brought in from Syria.
这不可能  你确定吗
That can't be true. You're sure?
由莱瑟比负责运送
Leatherby's the courier.
我需要知道时间地点
I need to know where and when.
我只是管钱的
I am just the money man.
那就请你尽心尽责
Well, then do your job.
付钱给莱瑟比  查明我要知道的事
Take Leatherby his payment and find out what I need to know.
一旦我开始发问
The moment I start asking questions--
就照我说的做
You'll do as I say.
我会在他的赌场跟他见面
I meet him at his casino, yeah--
"战后地"赌场  明天凌晨三点
Apres La Guerre, tomorrow morning, 3 A.M.,
以未切割的钻石作为报酬
pay him in uncut diamonds.
就这么多了
That's it.
你得带上窃听器
You'll wear a wire.
然后暴露自己的身份?
And have my cover blown?
我才不理会什么上级命令
I don't give a shit what the chain of command want
或是中情局的屁话
or what the CIA believe.
你要是敢骗我们  我就把你给阉了
If you're playing us, I'll have you castrated
绝不能让我手下再受伤害
before I see another one of those men hurt.
你疯了  上校
You're out of control, Major.
要我说  将造成你手下伤亡的人
For the record, it's you, not me,
是你  而不是我
that's gonna get your people killed.
你恨我  不是吗
You hate me, don't you?
-詹姆士  -别说话
- James-- - Don't.
觉得我跟那群混蛋一样
Just one of a long line of bastards,
是吧
aren't I,
跑来这鬼地方
men that come out here
抱怨这太热太脏
and moan about the heat and the dust
却又到处寻欢作乐
whilst taking whatever the fuck they like.
英国人
The English--
英国人喜欢吹嘘
The English like to bang on
他们那该死的帝国
about the fucking Empire
那辉煌时代
and the glory days,
唧唧歪歪的狗屁东西
and yada, yada, fucking yada,
但那鬼地方是我们苏格兰人发现的
but it was us Scots who found it,
是我们攻占  并为他们的守住的
took it, and held it for them.
为什么
Why?
我们喜爱偏远的地方
We love these faraway places,
陌生的人
these faraway people.
纯属情不自禁
Can't help ourselves.
你有什么要告诉我的吗
Have you got anything to tell me?
有什么要说的吗
Anything at all?
前特种空勤团成员  自九十年代末
Ex-SAS, operating out of Beirut
开始在贝鲁特从事军火
since the late Nineties, smuggles weapons,
毒品的走私活动  非法敛财
drugs, dirty money.
这些我们都知道
Yeah. We know all that.
海湾战争前他的档案都是清白的
Before Iraq, this guy's record was impeccable.
是嘛  我的也是
Oh, yeah? So was mine.
我只想知道到底出了什么事
I just want to know what went wrong,
使他变成了现在的这样
what turned that man into this man.
得了吧  迈克
Come on, Mike.
年轻人总会改变  有的变好
Young people change, sometimes for good...
有的变坏
sometimes bad.
第一次海湾战争期间
During the first Gulf War,
他曾在伊拉克深入敌后作战
he was operating behind Iraqi lines,
遭到了共和国卫队军官的
where he was captured and tortured
逮捕和拷问
by officers of the Republican Guard.
这可能就是原因所在
Yeah. Maybe that's it.
总部  我们已就位
Zero, we are in position,
未发现目标
no visual on target.
重复  未发现目标
I repeat, no visual on target.
请下注
Place your bets.
发现莱瑟比
Leatherby in play.
擅离职守啊  士兵
AWOL, soldier?
偷偷跑出来的
Lucky escape.
要为人民服务
Ah, Tommy this, Tommy that.
你的政治觉悟哪去了
How's your fucking soul, huh?
但是听着  聪明的朋友
But here's the thing, my bright-eyed friend.
杀手就是杀手
A killer is a killer,
一个男人也许可以逃避很多事
and a man may escape many things...
但绝不能逃避自己
but never himself.
我们俩想法一致
You and I have had the same fortune cookie.
优秀的士兵都心有灵犀
All good soldiers are bound for hell.
只是有些人明白  有些人糊涂
It's just that some see it, and others don't.
命中注定的事情逃不得
Whit's fur ye'll no go past ye.
干杯
Cheers.
拿些酒来
Bring some wine.
你如果想找点事做
You want some work, Heh.
给我打电话
you give me a call, eh...
随时联系
or give me a call, anyway.
不下注了  不玩了
No more bets. No more bets.
谢谢
Cheers.
想喝一杯吗
You want a drink?
不  谢谢  我已经有了
No, thanks. I got one.
能请我喝一杯吗
You want to buy me one?
我很乐意  但是不行
I would love to, but I can't.
给我打电话
Call me.
停止下注
No more bets.
卡马里来了
Kamali in play.
安全起见
Just to be careful.
我这辈子杀的第一个人是位阿根廷士兵
Killed my first man with a knife--
用刀干掉的
Argentinean conscript.
那时真他妈冷
It was so fucking cold,
刀刃上的血都结冰了
the blood froze on the blade.
想象一下
Imagine that.
十七年后  我躺在床上
Seventeen years later, I'm lying in bed,
翻过身  你等等
I roll over--wait--
那个混蛋竟然还在
and the bastard is there
他躺在我旁边  对着我笑
lying next to me, smiling at me,
他妈的对着我笑
just fucking smiling at me.
做噩梦的总是士兵
It's always the soldiers that have the nightmares,
他们被派去干肮脏的活
they send in to do all the filthy work.
你的双手没沾过鲜血
No blood under your fingernails,
沾过没有?
or is there?
我听说哥伦比亚死了很多人  李奥
Heard a lot of men died in Colombia, Leo.
东西带了吗
Do you have them?
另外一半等人送到了再给
The other half once the package is safely delivered.
我要知道他什么时候来  从哪儿来
I need to know when and where it's coming in.
你为什么要知道这些
Why would you want to know that?
别问这么多  天呐
Don't push it. Come on.
因为我需要做些安排
Because I've been told to make arrangements.
无意冒犯  詹姆士
No offense, James.
你只是个抱着昔日战事不放的送货员
You're just a fucking delivery boy peddling old war stories.
告诉我需要知道的情报才是乖孩子
Tell me what I need to know-- there's a good boy--
否则我看你就别再为朱海瑞卖命了
or I'll see you never work for al-Zuhari again.
坐
Sit.
你以为这就吓到我了?
Think you scare me?
不是吧
Really?
拿枪做什么
Why the gun?
以示强调
Emphasis.
卧底已暴露
Asset's compromised.
总部  我们是否要救他出来
Zero, are we gonna pull him out, or what?
让他自己处理
Leave him in play.
是  长官
Yes, ma'am.
-我下注  -好的  先生
- Buy me in. - Yes, sir.
李奥  这是我和我对象的私事
Leo, this was a matter between me and my boy.
跟酒保有一腿?
A fucking barman?
不  没有的事
No. It's nothing!
再让我看到你的脸  我就割了它
I see your face in here again, I'll cut it off.
-抱歉  -去你妈的
- Sorry. - For fuck's sake.
别  别  别
No, no, no, no!
天呐
Oh, God!
现在才算没事
Now it's nothing.
李奥  我只想让你知道
Leo, I just wanted you to know
我对待背叛的态度
what I feel about betrayal.
他和我只是朋友
He's just a friend.
你只属于我
You belong to me.
最好搞清楚这点
Best get that seen to.
不
No!
你要是想死请便
You want to get yourself killed, go ahead.
鬼门关我绕过了  不干了  退出
I'm through. I'm done. I'm out.
我们看到他了
We've got him.
发现他对象  看上去像是中了一枪
Eyes on the boyfriend. Looks like he took a bullet.
带他回来
Bring him in.
进去  不然打烂你另一只手
Get in, or I shoot the other one.
干什么  干什...
What? Wha--
卡马里  把枪放下
Kamali, put that gun down.
你们他妈在这做什么
What the fuck are you doing here?
爸
Dad.
这些人是谁
阿嬷  没事的
Amma, everything is fine.
带艾斯特回你的房间去
Take Ester and go back to your room.
-爸  到底发生了什么  -艾斯特  拜托
- Dad, what is going on? - Ester, please.
马上跟阿嬷回她房间去
Go with Amma back to her room now.
卡马里  下来把枪给我
Kamali, I need you to come down here and give me that gun.
还有烟吗
You got a spare?
喂  你多大了
Oi, how old are you?
你谁啊  我妈吗
What are you, my mom?
他只是长的比较像老妈子
Eh, he just looks like one.
你们跟我爸是怎么认识的
So how do you two know my dad?
这就说来话长了
Eh, it's kind of a long story.
我懂  我还小
I get it. I'm young.
碰撞乐队是吧
The Clash, huh?
最喜欢哪张专辑
Got a favorite album?
《伦敦呼声》  别转移话题
"London Calling," And don't try and change the subject.
你呢  老妈子
How about you, ma?
性爱手枪乐队
Sex Pistols.
-真的假的  -没错
- Really? - Yeah.
我以为你喜欢威猛乐队
I would've taken you as a Wham kind of guy.
安德鲁·维治利的才华被过分低估了
Andrew Ridgely is hugely underrated.
安德鲁·维治利: 威猛乐队成员
看来你...  作为十三岁的孩子来说
So you got it pretty together for a,
算是相当成熟了?
what, thirteen-year-old?
别对我指手画脚
Don't tell me.
你以前也认识像我这样的孩子
You used to know a kid who was just like me,
那个人就是你自己
and it was...you.
过来  把那给我
Come here. Give me that.
你以为你是谁啊
Who do you think you are?
吸烟有害健康
Smoking will kill you.
你很会讨孩子欢心  是吧
You're really good with kids, aren't you?
我以前也那熊样
Been there and done that.
我们得好好谈谈
We should have a talk.
我说了我不干了  离开...
I told you, I'm done, leaving--
他的地盘  这座城市  所有这一切
his place, this city, all of it.
你们的长官刚刚让我跟那个
Your commanding officer just shoved me into a room
精神失常的反社会分子共处一室
with a delusional sociopath and a list of questions
还让我追问一系列足以勾起他疑心的问题
guaranteed to fuel his fucking paranoia.
总之  这不仅涉及我的个人安危
Anyway, it's not just about me.
我还得顾及艾斯特
I have to think of Ester.
如果真主党发现你是莱瑟比的对象
If Hezbollah found out you and Leatherby were lovers,
你就完蛋了
you'd be dead.
如果你帮我  我也自会帮你
If you help me, I will help you.
没人帮得了我
我们可以帮你搞定签证
We can get you a visa,
给你新的生活  外加报酬
a new life, some money.
作为回报  你要告诉我们
And in return, you can tell us
莱瑟比会在何时何地
when and where Leatherby's going to be bringing
带朱海瑞过境
Al-Zuhari over the border.
我不能告诉你们
I can't.
那我只能去告诉真主党你是个娘泡
Then I'll just have to tell Hezbollah that you're a manyook,
但在真主党知道这件事之前
but before Hezbollah know,
我会确保让你父亲耳闻你的羞耻作风
I'll make sure your father hears of your shame.
接吧
Answer it.
詹姆士来电
喂  什么事
Yeah. What is it?
回家来
你自己决定
So you decide.
在克夫拉亚外有个机场
There's an air field just outside Kefraya
詹姆士经常使用
James uses...
他们会在明天中午过来
and they will come tomorrow at noon.
你要去哪
So where would you go?
有很多选择
There are options.
我一直在计划外逃
I always planned to get out.
没人可以一直这样活下去
Nobody can live this kind of life forever.
必须对将来做好计划  找好出路
You must have plans for the future, a way out.
在某人逼我们下跪
Is that before somebody pushes us to our knees
用子弹打穿我们脑袋之前吗
and puts a bullet in that back of our head
就像你对巴克斯特那样
like you did with Baxter?
迈克尔
Michael...
出于正确的动机杀了错误的对象
Would it have been the first time
这种事难道你们没做过吗
that you'd killed the wrong person for the right reason?
我不会假装理解  更不会假装喜欢你这种人
I'm not gonna pretend I understand or even like a man like you.
你得把你挑起的事给了结了
You need to finish what you started.
你说起来倒是轻松
Easy for you to say.
像你这种人还剩下些什么可以舍弃
What do men like you have to lose?
我已失去了我曾经拥有的东西
What I had, I lost.
你觉得值吗
Was it worth it?
如果我继续卧底  道尔顿那怎么处理
If I come back, what about Dalton?
她是个大麻烦
She's a liability.
没错
Yeah.
这件事交给我们  李奥
We got your back on that, Leo.
中情局的档案里没有提到任何关于孩子的事
File from the CIA didn't mention anything about a kid.
如果能一直瞒下去  我会很感激的
And I'll appreciate it if we could keep it that way.
好吧
All right.
她妈妈怎么了
What happened to her mother?
死了
She died.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
我们会帮你渡过难关的  李奥
We'll get you through this, Leo.
好吧
Ok.
赶紧离开我家吧
Now get the fuck out of my house.
我们会在机场跑道的南面
We'll set up an armed support
设立一个武装支援队
towards the south side of the airstrip.
-你看这地图...  -好的
- If you look at the map... - Ok.
这是什么
What's all this?
结果呢?
And?
卡马里同意继续当卧底
Kamali's still in.
我们有情报
We have intel.
他对象开口了
The boyfriend talked.
莱瑟比将使用这个机场带朱海瑞入境
Leatherby's bringing al-Zuhari in through this airfield.
这就是我们行动的依据
So that's what we're going in on,
他对象的一面之词?
the boyfriend's word?
我们可以征求卡马里的意见
We could run it past Kamali.
不
No.
长官
Ma'am,
洛克上校知道你的决定吗
does Colonel Locke know about this?
行动后再对洛克进行简报
Locke will be briefed post-op.
你他妈跟卡马里到底有什么过节
What's your fucking problem with Kamali?
我们都知道他做了什么  以及他那么做的原因
We all know what he did and why he did it,
而事实在于  将巴克斯特送到
but the truth is, you're the one that put Baxter
枪口面前的人是你
in front of that gun.
你们觉得李奥·卡马里这种人是怎么活到今天的?
How do you think a man like Leo Kamali survives, hmm?
很简单
It's simple.
正所谓墙头草两头倒
He sells himself as whatever you need him to be--
他可以当中情局卧底  也可以当恐怖分子
CIA asset, terrorist,
还可以帮别人洗钱
money launderer.
他今天当了你们的谁啊  新交的闺密?
So what the fuck were you buying today, huh, new best friend?
这次任务非胜即败
This is a one-shot deal.
一旦搞砸了  朱海瑞就会人间蒸发
We screw up, and al-Zuhari is gone,
再想抓他的话  一切都迟了
and we don't see him again until it's too late.
这任务你们到底出不出
So are you in, or you out?
长官  飞机几点降落
Ma'am, what time's that plane land?
明天中午
Tomorrow at noon.
我得见心理医生去
Gonna see my shrink.
很高兴你联系了我
Pleased you called me
家里有女人吗?
You have girl at home?
没女人
No girl...
也没家
and no home.
真是个忧伤的故事
Sad story.
说不定咱俩会有美满的结局  你说呢?
Maybe there's happy ending for you and me, huh?
也许吧
Yeah.
刚才爽不爽  猛男
You like that, tough guy?
你在这工作?  在贝鲁特工作?
So you work out of here? Beirut?
-我是个艺术家  -哈哈
- I'm artist. - Ha ha ha!
别笑  我证明给你看
No laugh. I prove.
好吧
Yeah.
瞧  艺术家签证
See? Artist visa.
又跳舞又脱衣服  这可不简单
To dance and take clothes off is not easy.
卡雅·谢尔盖耶维奇·塔拉索夫
So, Katya Sergeyevich Tarasov,
你怎么会来这么远的地方
how come you're so far from home?
我借了些钱开公司
I borrow some money to set up business.
酿成大错  遇到了坏人
Big mistake. Bad man.
唐·柯里昂:  《教父》中的大反派
遇到唐·柯里昂了
How you say? Don Corleone?
你还是说遇到黑手党比较实在
Mafia.
所以我才来跳舞
So I dance,
攒钱还他
save money to pay him back,
否则他会打断我的腿
or he break legs.
-欠了多少  -一万美金
- How much? - $10,000.
那你得跳不少场啊
Fucking lot of dancing.
我喜欢跳舞
I like to dance.
我也喜欢我的腿
I like my legs.
是啊  我也喜欢
Yeah. I do, too.
我们到时候见?  你住哪
I will see you? Where you stay?
还是我打电话找你吧
Heh. I'll call you.
回头见咯  美腿
See you around, sexy legs.
总部  正在接近目标位置
Zero, approaching position,
距离克夫拉亚机场一公里
one click from Kefraya airstrip.
开始行动
Let's do this.
该死
Shit.
准备  目标护卫队正在接近
We're on. Target convoy approaching.
四辆厢式车正向你方移动
Four SUVs heading your way.
收到  我已就位
Roger that. I'm in position.
我从这能看到你那大屁股
I can see your sorry ass from here.
-我看见你了  -我也是
- I have eyes on you. - Yeah. I see you, too.
飞机正在盘旋  准备降落
Bird is circling to land.
B1  我看见飞机了
Bravo One, I have eyes on the bird.
重复  我看见飞机了
I repeat, I have eyes on the bird.
该死
Shit.
B2  我看见莱瑟比了
Bravo Two, I got eyes on Leatherby.
我这有敌军若干
I have multiple X-rays.
我看见有人从飞机上下来
Yeah. I got someone stepping off that bird now.
无法识别目标
It's impossible to I.D. him.
B1  汇报
Bravo One, report.
无法识别目标
That's a negative on an I.D.
射击视野不清
I have no clear shots on X-rays.
移动到更好的射击角度
Moving for a better visual.
B1  回复
Bravo One, come in.
那是什么叼情况
What the fuck is that?
B1  回复  迈克
Bravo One, come in. Mike.
F  这里是S  掩护我们撤退  完毕
Foxhound, this is Sunray. Cover our exfil. Over.
撤
Move!
B1
Bravo One?
迈克  你没事吧
Mike, you all right?
-妈的  -该死
- Fuck. - Shit.
总部  莱瑟比持有目标
Zero, Leatherby has the target.
重复  朱海瑞在莱瑟比手上
Repeat, Leatherby has al-Zuhari.
B1  回复
Bravo One, come in.
该死
Ow! Shit.
-我是B1  -迈克  你没事吧
- Bravo One... - Mike, you all right?
我没事  正在撤退
I'm fine. I'm on the move.
抄近路
Cut across!
我来了  别跑的跟娘们儿似的
I got you. Stop running like a girl.
-上来了  快开快开  -你没事吧
- OK. Go, go, go, go. - Good?
嗯  我没事
Yeah. I'm OK. I'm good.
你这车开的像老妇女  快开
You drive like a pussy. Move.
-B4开始移动  -收到
- Bravo Four on the move. - Copy.
B组  目标正向机场南部移动
Bravo team. Target heading south of airfield.
收到  正向你方靠近
Copy that. Coming to you.
两点钟方向有情况
Coming up on our two o'clock.
该死的
Goddamn it.
抓稳
Hold on.
雷区
斯科特  你看见了吗
Scott, did you see that?
什么
What?
那块牌子上写着"雷区"
Fucking sign that said, "Mines."
那该怎么办  减速吗
What should I do? Should I slow down?
不  继续开
No. Keep going.
这里没有地雷  迈克
There's no mines here, Mike.
那肯定是以前的警告牌
It must be an old sign.
不  或许他们排雷漏了一个
Nope. Maybe they missed one.
开快点  快点
Go faster. Go faster.
好啦  知道了
All right, all right, all right.
他妈的
Fuck!
不  或许漏了两个
Nope. Maybe it's two.
赶紧驶离雷区  好吗
Getting us off here, all right?
B1  你在什么位置
Bravo One, what is your position?
看见他们了
Ah, there they are.
跟他并排开
Just get up alongside.
接着
There you go.
送给你了  伙计
Have that, mates.
他妈的
Fuck.
你们必须活捉朱海瑞
You have to take al-Zuhari alive.
该死
Shit.
斯科特  我没子弹了
Scott! Yo, I'm out of ammo!
斯科特
Scott!
进入战斗
Taking!
B1正遭受攻击  没有发现目标
Bravo One is taking fire. No visual on target.
斯科特
Scott!
干嘛
What?
前进
Moving!
他妈的
Fuck!
那是我们的目标车辆
That's our target vehicle!
确认目标
Confirm target.
这不是目标  只有一个女性
That's a negative. It's a female.
不是目标  只有一个女性
Negative. It's a female.
该死
Shit.
朱海瑞不在这  重复  他不在这
Al-Zuhari is not here. I repeat, not here.
如果朱海瑞开始行动
Well, if al-Zuhari's moving,
不管他在计划什么  很快就会付诸实施
then whatever he's planning must be happening soon.
麻烦告诉我  你这烂摊子至少有些成果
Please tell me you got something to show for this mess.
带她回来
Bring her in.
斯科特  撤
Scott! Moving!
撤
Move!
跟我走
Come on.
我们俩想法一致
You and I got the same fortune cookie.
我要知道他什么时候来  从哪儿来
I need to know when and where it's coming in.
詹姆士  救我出去  这车要爆炸了
Aah! James, get me out! It's gonna blow! Hey!
詹姆士  詹姆士  救命
James! James, help!
撤  快撤
Go, go, go, go, go!
快撤  我们撤
Go, go, go! Let's go!
狗日的叛徒  给我把卡马里抓来
Fucking traitor! Find me Kamali.
好了  照我说的做  站好
OK. OK. Follow my voice. Stand up.
转过身去
Turn your back against...
操  这简直是胡闹
Fuck, This is fucking bullshit.
我要你站好
I need you to stand up...
我没做错事
I've done nothing wrong.
往前走
OK. Move forward.
往哪...
Where--
安静  安静一点
Quiet. Be quiet.
我父亲是塔雷克·阿布德
My father is Tareq Abboud.
我叫索菲亚·阿布德  我父亲是塔雷克·阿布德
My name is Sofia Abboud. My father is Tareq Abboud.
我不该被抓到这儿来
I shouldn't be here. I shouldn't be here.
带她到楼下去
Take her downstairs.
求求你  这是个严重的错误
Please. This is a terrible mistake.
往前走
Move forward.
不  求求你
No, please!
没事的
It's alright.
他是个商人
He's a businessman.
他花钱把我弄出叙利亚
He paid to get me out of Syria.
一派胡言  快说  你到底是谁
Bullshit, come on. Who are you, really?
停手吧  少校
Stand down, Major.
你搞什么
What the fuck?
请把这位女士带到其他地方去
Will you take this woman somewhere else, please?
是
Sir.
请
Please...
上校  我认为那个女人...
Colonel, I believe that woman to be--
那个女人说的是实话
Is exactly who she said she is.
她父亲在2007年之前是阿萨德的财务大臣
Her father was Assad's finance minister until 2007.
有传言说他可能为朱海瑞提供了资金
It was rumored that he might provide al-Zuhari with funding,
但仅此而已
but that's it.
她肯定是个送情报的
She has to be a courier.
你知道他们会动用女人
You know that they use women
和家庭成员来传递情报
and family members to carry messages.
我知道
I know.
她会被审讯的  但不是由你主持
She'll be processed, just not by you.
你派我来执行这个任务
You sent me on this operation.
我卧底了三个月
I've been undercover for three months.
巴克斯特他...
Baxter--
你不能让我退出  菲利普
You can't take this away from me, Philip.
如果朱海瑞在那架飞机上
If al-Zuhari had been on that plane--
但他不在  不是吗
But he wasn't, was he?
你冒的风险大到不合情理  瑞秋
You're taking unjustifiable risks, Rachel.
你的决策不明智
You're making bad calls.
导致其他战友死亡只是时间问题
It's only a matter of time before someone else is killed.
你不能这样做
You can't fucking do this.
少校  你将无限期休假
Major, consider yourself on extended leave,
即刻生效
effective immediately.
都听着
OK. Listen up.
从现在开始  我将直接指挥该小组
As of this moment, I'm taking direct command of this unit.
明白
Sir. Sir.
吗啡
好了  索菲亚  我们来谈谈
OK, Sofia. Let's talk.
我的老天
Oh, Jesus Christ.
我带你兜风  然后好好谈谈
We're gonna take a drive, and then we're gonna talk,
在此期间  我要你记住一件事
and as we do, I want you to bear one thing in mind--
我现在一无所有
I have absolutely nothing to lose.